<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robert Ferrante</title>
    <link>http://rferrante.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Robert Ferrante</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2015 by Robert Ferrante</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 13:50:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://rferrante.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The cons Package</title>
      <link>http://rferrante.github.io/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 13:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rferrante.github.io/post/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve shared the repo for my &lt;strong&gt;cons&lt;/strong&gt; package. It&amp;rsquo;s written in Go and is aimed at helping create console programs in Go, of the type that loop and interpret your commands until you exit. The &lt;em&gt;cons&lt;/em&gt; package also includes some color support to make it a bit easier to use colors in your text output and/or your prompt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The package has no external dependencies, that is, outside of the Go standard package library. So it&amp;rsquo;s easy to go get and start using in your program. There are a lot of packages around that do the same thing, and I&amp;rsquo;m not about to think mine is better than anyone else&amp;rsquo;s. I do use it myself though, and to me it seems just about right. If I like using it, maybe someone else will to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find out more about it at (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rferrante/cons&#34;&gt;https://github.com/rferrante/cons&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://rferrante.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 13:47:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rferrante.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Robert Ferrante (rferrante). I am a software engineer. I think I&amp;rsquo;m of the old school; I consider it a profession, a craft, and a discipline. I am currently learning Go, and I&amp;rsquo;m sharing some software on Github. I started out working in C, moving into Objective-C, VB, Java, then C# for a while, followed by Python. There is something to be said for them all, but Go feels like home now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>